<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>stoffie.github.io</title><link>https://stoffie.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on stoffie.github.io</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://stoffie.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Professional Summary</title><link>https://stoffie.github.io/post/1-professional-summary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://stoffie.github.io/post/1-professional-summary/</guid><description>Agile Software Developer with a passion for building great final products. Adept at utilizing any language and cloud technology to meet client specifications working in a fast moving team. Always looking for new challenges.</description></item><item><title>Core Qualifications</title><link>https://stoffie.github.io/post/2-core-qualification/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://stoffie.github.io/post/2-core-qualification/</guid><description> Exceptional Agile skills in any situation. Excellent communication and presentation skills. Dedicated team player. Reliable full stack developer developer. Able to create and reason about cloud architecture designs that make sense.</description></item><item><title>Experience</title><link>https://stoffie.github.io/post/3-experience/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://stoffie.github.io/post/3-experience/</guid><description>Full Remote Software Engineer who has been working from home since 2021. 5 years of experience solving challenges while working in startups.</description></item><item><title>Education &amp; Certifications</title><link>https://stoffie.github.io/post/4-education/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://stoffie.github.io/post/4-education/</guid><description>Università degli Studi di Trento. Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree. Information Technology.
Certified AWS System Architect Associate, Google Cloud Engineer and Terraform Engineer.</description></item><item><title>Languages</title><link>https://stoffie.github.io/post/5-languages/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://stoffie.github.io/post/5-languages/</guid><description>Confident English speaker and writer. Italian mother tongue.</description></item><item><title>Skills</title><link>https://stoffie.github.io/post/6-skills/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://stoffie.github.io/post/6-skills/</guid><description>Typescript, Javascript, Vue.js, Vue.x, React, Responsive HTML and SCSS, Node.js, Express, Java, Kotlin, Spring Boot, Hibernate, PostgreSQL, AWS, Microservices, Linux, Docker, Gitlab, Vert.x, golang, python, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, IBM Blockchain Platform, Ruby, RubyOnRails, Intellij.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://stoffie.github.io/readme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stoffie.github.io/readme/</guid><description>Damiano Stoffie Senior Full Stack Engineer Professional Summary Experienced Full Stack Engineer with extensive remote work experience since 2021, seeking to join a diverse and polyglot team that excels in leadership, communication, and Agile methodologies. I am proficient in multiple programming languages and frameworks such as Typescript, Java, Kotlin, Spring Boot, Node.js, and Express. My expertise includes cloud architectures and microservices, and I thrive in fast-paced team environments.
I hold several prestigious IT certifications: AWS Solutions Architect Associate, Google Cloud Engineer, and Terraform Associate Engineer.</description></item></channel></rss>